{
    "id": "a2c7620d1ea646df9fc1d332c61a24d1",
    "title": "Nouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "That kind of movies doesn’t give me any ........................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "amuse",
                "amusement",
                "amusing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cc2b515003064f2087e8a187879974f3"
        },
        {
            "question": "The .................................. of this article is $",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cost",
                "costs"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e17a9b6932684099b32e014df61ecef2"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a .................................. to his family.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "disgrace",
                "disgraceful",
                "disgraced"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ecbc2337135a48a18394814687531224"
        },
        {
            "question": "He put up a brave .........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fighting",
                "fight"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b5505258d4634d2c9ca0b1b63668b636"
        },
        {
            "question": "He gave a curt .....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "reply",
                "replied",
                "replying"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "47a5ffc0e006454eaabf72b7f89ca04f"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is a slight .................................. between these two shades.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "difference",
                "different",
                "differ"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "51c6bd98155a4ac8b1e1435a5fca1f2e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I see him ..................................",
            "description": "Daily is an adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "daily",
                "every day"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "27551877e4ff4181bd937f178d8b5091"
        },
        {
            "question": "He read the letter with .....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "care",
                "caring",
                "careful"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2b69daaefc55431c85e8358cede175a2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Though the ant is small it has as much ..................................... as the elephant.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "intelligence",
                "intelligent",
                "intelligently"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ffd60a625d3e4d73826e0717aa387566"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is so industrious that he wins everybody’s .......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "admiration",
                "admire",
                "admiringly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bf49f53ce6364e7c96e91055e31c7f88"
        }
    ]
}